
var cars = [
    {make: "Ford",
    models: ["Ranger", "Bronco", "F-150"]},

    {make: "Chevy",
    models: ["Silverado", "Trailblazer", "S-10"]}
];

var questionBankArray = [
    {question: "In the Terminal, what do you type to move into a different directory?", 
    choices: [
        "md", "cd", "vinyl", "cassette tape"
    ],
    correctIndex: 1},

    {question: "In the Terminal, what key(s) do you press to autocomplete?",
    choices: [
        "tab", "shift + tab", "up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A", "backtick"
    ],
    correctIndex: 0},

    {question: "In VS Code, what is the shortcut to commenting out code?",
    choices: [
        "command + C", "command + space", "command + /", "command + tab"
    ],
    correctIndex: 2},

    {question: "em is relative to the ____________.",
    choices: [
    "parent", "child", "grandmother", "Cousin Eddie"
    ],
    correctIndex: 0},

    {question: "What property makes the element take up the full width of its parent?",
    choices: [
        "display: inline", "display: block", "display: full", "display: parent"
    ],
    correctIndex: 1},

    {question: "position: absolute takes the element out of the document ____________.",
    choices: [
        "body", "window", "display", "flow"
    ],
    correctIndex: 3},

    {question: "How do you remove bullet points from a ul?",
    choices: [
        "list.display.type = none", "list-style-type: none", "list.style(none)", "It is not possible."
    ],
    correctIndex: 1},

    {question: "In flexboxes, justify content is on the ___ axis, while align items is on the ___ axis.",
    choices: [
        "X, Y", "Y, X", "A, B", "Earth, Mars"
    ],
    correctIndex: 0},

    {question: "What index would you use to access “Cassandra” in the following array names = [“Cassandra” , “Nick”, “Bernadette”]",
    choices: [
        0, 1, 2, 3
    ],
    correctIndex: 0},
    {question: "Which is the correct way to call a function?", 
    choices: [
        "myFuction: myArgument", "myFuction = myArgument", "myFunction(myArgument)", "my Function (my Argument)"
    ],
    correctIndex: 2},
];


// --------------------
// AskBCS Learning Assistant, 13MAR2023 
// var letters = [
//     {capital: "A", small: "a"},
//     {capital: "B", small: "b"},
// ];
// console.log(letters[0].small);

// console.log(questionBankArray[0].question);
 